<blog>
	<post>
		<date>November 28, 2022</date>
		<author>Sai Kiran</author>
		<title>Recognizing Signs and Symptoms of Seasonal Affective Disorder.</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://images.ctfassets.net/h8qzhh7m9m8u/3VobuvkO6KVEJr83zA3nPn/e3e9fd8e6372fb1dd6c459ef01bd6527/SAD.jpg</image_path>
			<text>Recognizing Signs and Symptoms of Seasonal Affective Disorder.</text>
		</summary>
		<body>While the fall and winter seasons bring colorful changes, they can also be a source of struggle for many. Seasonal affective disorder,
		 or SAD (aptly named), is defined as a type of depression that results from the change in seasons. 
		It's common to experience seasonal blues, but you do not have to suffer in silence.
		The first step to combatting seasonal depression is to recognize the signs and symptoms associated with SAD.
		</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>December 2, 2022</date>
		<author>Sai Kiran</author>
		<title>How to Do the Russian Twist for Powerful Abs</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://hips.hearstapps.com/hmg-prod/images/russian-twist-sharpened-1548270008.jpg?crop=1.00xw:0.898xh;0,0.0310xh&resize=1200:*</image_path>
			<text>How to Do the Russian Twist for Powerful Abs.</text>
		</summary>
		<body>If you listed the most popular ab exercises, there would be some familiar contenders like crunches, planks, and leg raises, no doubt. 
		But one dark horse in the race is the Russian twist.
		You'll see it performed by bodybuilders, fitness influencers,
		“functional fitness” athletes who wear toe-gripping shoes that look like gloves, group-fitness worshipers, and cardio enthusiasts.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>December 3, 2022</date>
		<author>Sai Kiran</author>
		<title>HOW TO MAKE CHICKEN FOR MEAL PREP</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://hips.hearstapps.com/hmg-prod.s3.amazonaws.com/images/fennel-roasted-chicken-and-peppers-1641421056.jpg</image_path>
			<text>HOW TO MAKE CHICKEN FOR MEAL PREP.</text>
		</summary>
		<body>
		In this method, you follow recipes using the seasoning or marinade and the cooking method for those recipes, but you just make the chicken several days ahead of making the rest.
		After you have your chicken breasts or thighs marinated or seasoned, keep the process simple with an easy cooking method of your choice.
        
		If you're a meal planner, this approach is right up your alley.
        The benefits of this method are that you get a variety of flavors and eliminate the questions later in the week about what you should make.
        You choose an ideal time for cooking. Weekends may be better time for cooking than weeknights,
        so by moving the bulk of your meal prep to a more convenient time you've made healthy eating more convenient.
        
		To get started, find some easy chicken recipes you enjoy. If you need some ideas,
        you'll want to try. Pick a day of the week when you have a bit more time to be in the kitchen - again, usually the weekend.
		Then pause the recipes after the chicken is prepped and finish the recipe off later in the week when you're ready to eat.
        Even though you're doing the same steps you could have done throughout the week, you'll be amazed at how this will reduce your total time in the kitchen, 
		and you'll be so much more empowered to make healthy eating choices when you have quick chicken on hand! Save on prep, cooking, and cleaning time when you knock out multiple meals at once.
		</body>
	</post>
</blog>